聽著
Listen!
停下
Stop!
你個該死的蠢貨
You silly fucking twit!
求你了
Please!
你就是一個愚蠢的婊子 你知道吧
You are one stupid fucking bitch, you know that?
閉上你的臭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
不
No.
你在這兒
There you are.
不
No!
No.
你這個小王八蛋
You're a little shit. No!
不
No!
祝你新工作一切順利
Good luck in your new job
安娜塔西雅-斯蒂爾
Anastasia Steele?
謝謝
Thanks.
克裡斯汀-格雷
CHRISTIAN GERY
嗯 好的我明白了 謝謝
Yeah. Got it. Thank you.
早上好 海德先生
Good morning, Mr. Hyde.
安娜 拜託 叫我傑克
Ana, please, it's Jack.
茶 沒記錯吧 淡紅茶
Tea, right? Weak, black.
其實應該是我去幫你買的
I'm pretty sure I'm supposed to get this for you,
不過謝謝了 傑克
but thank you, Jack.
巴巴多斯島太美了
Barbados is amazing.
到處是美麗的珊瑚 海龜 和美酒
It's all coral and turtles and booze...
你應該來著看看的 為什麼你沒來呢
Oh! You should be here. Why aren't you here?
告訴我那個討厭鬼弟弟
Yeah, and tell that douchebag brother of mine
他應該休休假了
to take a day off for once, would ya?
好的 再見 安娜
All right. Bye, Ana. Bye!
新工作怎麼樣
Carla". So, how's the newjob?
很好 我的上司很重視我的提議
It's good. My boss has me weighing in on submissions.
那就太好了
That's exciting. Great.
你有克裡斯汀的消息麼
Have you heard from Christian?
是的
Yeah.
他送過花給我
He sent me flowers.
祝我好運吧
To wish me luck.
親愛的
Sweetheart,
你什麼時候告訴我你們之間發生了什麼
are you ever gonna tell me what happened between you?
本質的區別,我猜
Fundamental differences, I guess.
一切都會過去的
It wasn't gonna last.
給我的工作？
Are those for me?
沒事 回頭做也不遲
Nah. They can wait.
好吧
Okay.
你看起來很漂亮 今晚要出門
Look nice. Going out tonight?
我朋友的攝影展開幕
Oh, urn, a friend of mine has a photography exhibition opening tonight.
我的走了
So, gonna go.
好
Good.
你讀那些手稿收貨如何
How did you make out with those manuscripts?
老實講很棒  有一位叫
Oh, really great, actually. This one, um...
博伊斯-福克斯的
Boyce fox.
我讀起來簡直愛不釋手
I couldn't put it down. It's so sharp.
文筆如此強烈有力 我覺得他很好
And relevant. And I think he's really got something.
你覺得是這樣？  是的
You think? Yeah.
好吧，我會看看
All right. I'll check it out. Great.
今晚玩的愉快點 安娜  謝謝
Have fun tonight, Ana. Thank you.
辛苦了今天
Thanks for today.
晚安 安娜
Good night, Hannah.
再見
Bye!
來杯酒？
Glass of chardonnay?
謝謝
Thanks. Mmm-hmm.
我的天
Oh, my god.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
安娜
Ana!
你真的來了
You made it.
何塞
Jose「.
感覺這裡到處都是我的照片
This is, like, so much of my face in here.
如果我不先斬後奏的話 你可能會說 我會不好意思的
Well, if I had asked, you would have been like, "I'm too shy."
是啊
Yeah.
不過 你
But you...
這是我最棒的作品
It's my best stuff.
這是
That's so...
你喜歡她們嗎？
Do you like them?
她們超大
They are super large.
等等
Hold on.
所有照片都已售出 買家是同一個人
All the portraits have sold to one man.
你沒開玩笑 沒
You're kidding! No.
看來有人喜歡這些照片
Well, somebody likes them.
他們把這六幅都買了
They just bought all six.
六幅
All six?
今晚我請客  好吧？
Dinner's on me tonight, okay? Mmm.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
安娜斯塔西婭
Anastasia.
是你 對吧 是你買了全部照片
It was you, wasn't it? You just went and bought all of these?
我不喜歡陌生人盯著你看
I don't like strangers gawking at you.
你為什麼來這裡
Why are you here?
為了你
For you.
嗨
Hey.
我們換個地方談談好嗎？
Can we talk somewhere private?
不行
No.
我不是很擅長這個 我從未
Look, I'm not very good at this. I've never had to...
我從未想過要再次嘗試
I've never wanted to try again.
克裡斯汀 我
Christian, I don't...
這不是個好主意 我們就聊聊
It's not a good idea. Let's talk.
好麼 就是只是單純的聊聊 拜託
Okay? Just talk, please.
和我一起吃頓晚餐
Have dinner with me.
好吧 我會和你吃晚餐
Okay, fine. I will have dinner with you.
因為我餓了
Because I'm hungry.
但我們只是聊聊 就這樣
But we are only talking and that is it.
等等
Hold on.
嘿 我要先走了
Hey. I'm gonna take off.
真的？ 你的照片很令人驚歎 何塞
Already? Your photos are so stunning, Jose.
謝謝 謝謝 我為你驕傲
Thank you. Thank you. I'm proud of you.
克裡斯汀 不能 不能這樣
Christian, I can't. I can't do this.
安娜
Christ, Ana.
好吧
Okay.
我有個建議。
I have a proposition.
只是來吃飯，我們只是聊聊。
Just come to dinner. We can talk.
需要再看看菜單麼
Would you like some more time?
不了  兩份五分熟牛排 加薯條和青菜
No. Two steaks, medium. Fries. Green vegetables.
我要藜麥沙拉
Um, actually, I'm gonna have the quinoa salad.
好吧
Fine.
兩杯西拉葡萄酒
And two glasses of the barossa valley shiraz.
我們只按瓶賣 先生
We only sell that by the bottle, sir.
那就來一瓶
A bottle then.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
謝謝
Thanks.
所以
So?
我們來聊聊吧
Let's talk.
我想要你回來
I want you back.
我想重新協商一些條款
I'd like to renegotiate terms.
但我看不到任何可能
But I don't see how.
你想要的那些東西 你說過你就是那樣的人
The things you want, you said that's the way you are.
但上回的事不會在發生了
But what happened last time, that's not gonna happen again.
你怎麼證明
How can you say that?
我知道我要求過你向我證明 我到底能奉陪到什麼程度 但
I know that I asked you to show me how far it can go,
你很享受你所造就的痛苦
but you were getting off on the pain you inflicted.
你就是那種性格
That's still in you.
我正在努力改變
I'm working on it.
改變什麼？
Working on what?
要是你一直不講出來 我根本做不到
I can't do this if you won't talk to me.
你想知道什麼
What do you wanna know?
一切
Everything.
好吧
Fine.
我們自己來
Yeah. We'll manage.
我的生母在我四歲時過世了
My birth mother died when I was four.
她是個癮君子
She was an addict. Crack.
你能想像到那時什麼情形
You can fill in the blanks.
你過去為什麼不告訴我
Why didn't you tell me that?
我說了
I did.
當時你睡著了
But you were asleep at the time.
好吧
Okay. Well, um...
通常來講
Generally,
良好的溝通是一個關鍵點
a key part of good communication
在於溝通雙方都神志清醒
is that both parties be conscious.
對於你的母親我深感抱歉
I'm really sorry about your mother.
那都過去了
It's in the past.
現在 我帶你來這裡商量
Now, I brought you here to negotiate.
你願意接受新的條件麼？
You're open to new terms?
沒有規則
No rules.
沒有懲罰
No punishments.
沒有規則 沒有懲罰
No rules, no punishments
而且再也沒有秘密
and no more secrets.
我能做到
I can do that.
你想要一段
You want a...
你想怎樣稱呼的？
What do you call it?
一段香草之戀
A vanilla relationship?
我的意思是我們 只做  你可以接受的事
I mean, we only do what you're comfortable with.
不過你需要哪些快感
But you need all those things.
我更需要你
I need you more.
斯蒂爾女士
Miss Steele.
謝謝 泰勒
Thanks, Taylor.
沒有附加條件
No strings attached.
有點扎扎的
This is spiky.
我喜歡
I like it.
我明天打電話給你
I'll call you tomorrow.
好吧
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
願你夢中有我
或許吧 謝謝今晚的晚餐 回見 寶貝
安娜 我最近聽到很多關於你的佳話
Ana, I've been hearing a lot of good things about you.
告訴你 莉茲
- Oh... - Told you, Liz.
這實際上是一個八卦
This one actually reads.
嘿 傑克
Hey, Jack.
人事主管到處轉悠是想搞什麼 我們有麻煩了麼
What's the head of hr doing lurking around? Are we in trouble?
不是我只是來給予一些 鼓勵
Not at all. I'm just here to encourage.
真的我覺得去洛裡喝上一輪能起到效果
Really? Well, I think a round of drinks at Lori's would do the trick.
抱歉 要開會 另找時間吧
Sorry. Meetings. Otherwise.
洛裡是誰
Who's Lori?
那是街旁的一家酒吧
Oh, it's a bar around the corner.
週五去酒吧是慣例
On. Fridays are a bit of a ritual.
你應該和我們一起來
You should come.
就是啊 多去認認人
Absolutely. Go network.
不行我是挺想去的 但是我今晚有別的約會
Oh, no, I would. I have plans tonight.
那就把你的約會對像一起叫來 我們小聚一下
So have your plan come along. Just for a quick one.
你好
Hello?
是
Yeah.
玩的開心點
Have fun.
安娜斯塔西婭
Anastasia.
抱歉我們以前見過麼？
I'm sorry. Have we met before?
沒關係
It's okay.
我只是個路人甲
I'm nobody.
嘿 洛裡酒吧在這邊
Hey. Lori's is this way.
來吧我請客
Come on, I'm buying.
好的 酒來了
All right. Here we go.
謝謝
Mmm. Thanks.
其他人呢
Where is everyone?
你知道  現在時間還很早
You know, it's still early.
你對博伊斯-福克斯的評價 很有意思
Your comments on boyce fox were interesting.
通常來講 我對政治恐怖小說 不是很感興趣
I'm not usually into political thrillers.
嗯 我覺得
Yeah, well, I think the parallels
但丁名作低於中的排比句很精彩 但我
with Dante's inferno are amazing, but...
不 你說服了我
No. You convinced me.
我正在讀
I'm reading.
哦 那很好
Oh. That's great.
嘿
Hi! Hey
嗨
um, uh...
克裡斯汀 這是傑克-海德
Christian, this is Jack Hyde.
我是她男朋友
I'm the boyfriend.
我是她上司
I'm the boss.
你想喝什麼 克裡斯
What will you have, Chris?
多謝 傑克
Thanks, Jack.
下次 再喝吧
Another time.
謝謝
Thanks.
下次在和
Another time.
我真不敢相信你剛剛竟那樣跟他講話
I can't believe you just talked to him like that.
他想要我的東西
He wants what's mine.
什麼是你的東西
What's yours?
你剛才那樣有點專橫
That's a little presumptuous.
他是我的上司 克裡斯汀 你的冷靜點
He's my boss, Christian. You gotta calm down.
冷靜真不是我的長處
Calm isn't really my forte.
我知道有些東西能幫到你
I know something that could help.
這和我想得不一樣
You know, this is not what I had in mind.
你上次購物什麼時候
When's the last time you went shopping?
一周前在休斯敦
Houston. A week ago.
你買了什麼
What'd you buy?
一家航空公司
An airline.
拿著
Here.
你的新歡口味
Your new favorite flavor.
打擾一下
Excuse me.
你需要幫忙麼
Do you need a hand with that?
我能搞定
I'll manage.
好的
Okay.
我知道你在做什麼
I know what you're doing.
什麼 我要成為一名廚神
What? I'm being a culinary mastermind.
其實你動動嘴就好了
You only have to ask.
我想我們應該慢慢來
I think we should take it slow.
好的
Okay.
好的好的
Okay. Okay.
和我說說sip公司的事
Tell me about sip.
情況如何
How's it going?
很順利
It's good.
傑克看起來對我的意見很感興趣
Jack seems genuinely interested in my opinion.
士氣怎麼樣
What's morale like?
士氣
Morale?
你是問我們會不會早晨
You mean, like, do we all sit in a circle
圍成一圈坐下來唱公司司歌？
and sing the company song in the morning?
公司管理如何？員工滿意麼
Ls the firm well managed? Are people happy?
天啊
Oh, my god.
怎麼了
What?
你想要收購sip
You're buying sip?
不 你不能那樣做 這是我的工作
No! You can't do that. That's my job.
你不能連我的事業都要介入
You can't start interfering in my career.
跟這個沒關係
It's not about that.
我想要進軍出版業 sip是個合適的選擇
I've wanted to move into publishing. They're the best fit.
你會成為我的上司
But you're gonna be my boss.
嚴格的說我會是你上司的上司的上司
Technically, I'll be your boss's boss's boss.
然而我會和我上司的上司的上司上床
And I'm gonna be sleeping with my boss's boss's boss.
現在 你在和他吵架
Right now, you're arguing with him.
是啊 他表現得像個混蛋
Yeah, because he's being an ass.
混蛋 你說真的
An ass. Really?
混蛋
Ass.
嘔
Ooh...
你知道這樣做越界了
You know that's off limits.
我需要知道哪些地方可以碰觸
I'm gonna need a road map.
我以為你想到慢慢來
I thought you wanted to take it slow.
你先要什麼安娜斯塔西婭
What do you want, Anastasia?
如果我們要溝通 你必須把你的想法告訴我
If we're to communicate, you have to tell me.
我想要你
I want you.
穿的有點多
I'm too dressed.
繼續
Keep going.
吻我
Kiss me.
您想要什麼 安娜塔西雅
What do you want, Anastasia?
我想要你
I want all of you.
為何一直沒有找別人
Why do you think you waited?
在性方面
For sex.
嗯
Mmm.
我一直在讀簡奧斯丁和勃朗特姐妹的著作
I was reading Austen and bronte
沒人能達到小說中的人物標準
and nobody ever measured up to that.
我想我在等待某種例外
I guess I was waiting for something exceptional.
然後我遇到了你
And then I met you.
奧斯丁女士
Would miss Austen
會同意這種事麼
approve of this?
我本來是很浪漫的
I was being romantic,
然後漸漸的被你奇怪的方式所分散
and then you just go and distract me with your kinky fuckery.
奇怪的方式？
"Kinky fuckery"? Mmm-hmm.
我不知道那是什麼意思但聽起來很像樣子
I don't know what that is, but I like the sound of it.
你看起來和很平靜 我不想叫醒你
You looked so peaceful. I didn't wanna wake you.
做早餐的食物不夠了
There's not much for breakfast,
除非你想吃剩飯
unless you want cold stir-fry.
算了
No. Mmm.
給你 因為旺達兒給我的支票 你應該收回去
Here. The check you gave me for Wanda, you should have it back.
你留著吧
Keep it.
我留著？這可是2萬4千美元
Keep it? It's $24,000.
嗯，我知道
Yeah, I know.
我每一刻鐘就能賺這麼多 你留著吧
I make that kind of money every 15 minutes. Keep it.
安德裡亞 早安
Andrea? Good morning.
能否請你把2萬4千美元 轉入安娜斯塔西婭-斯蒂爾女士的賬戶
Could you please transfer $24,000 into the account of miss Anastasia Steele?
不 你在幹什麼
No! What are you doing?
沒事 謝謝
That's fine. Thank you.
為什麼你知道我的賬戶信息
Why do you have my bank account details?
這附近哪家早點比較好
What's good for breakfast around here?
克裡斯汀 你怎麼知道我的銀行賬戶信息
Christian, how do you have my bank information?
謝謝
Thank you.
手還能再快點才夠看 格雷
Gotta be quicker than that, grey.
我父母奧舉辦一場慈善舞會今晚
My parents are hosting a charity ball tonight.
我答應他們我會出席
I promised I'd make an appearance.
我希望你能和我一起
Want you to come with me.
我從沒參加過舞會
I've never been to a ball.
我沒有舞會穿的禮服
I don't have a dress for that.
還有 我的髮型該怎麼辦
Also, what am I gonna do with my hair?
我知道一個沙龍
I know a salon.
而且你不用擔心禮服的事
And you don't need to worry about a dress.
一切我都會處理好
It's all gonna be taken care of.
怎麼了
What is it? Um...
哪裡剛才有個女孩
There was just a girl over there.
她昨天在我的辦公室外面
And she was outside my office yesterday.
她知道我的名字
And she knew my name.
手腕上纏著繃帶 她很古怪
And she had a bandage on her wrist. It was really strange.
我們該走了
We should go.
現在
Just now.
是的
Yeah.
隨時告訴我
Keep me informed.
你知道那個女孩 克裡斯汀
You know that girl, Christian?
我來處理 什麼意思
I'm handling it. What does that mean?
我不想讓你擔心  相信我
I don't want you to worry about it. Trust me.
嗯
Um...
嘿 過的怎麼樣？
Hey, how are you doing?
很好  好的 我女朋友在這裡
Good, okay. So, uh, my girlfriend's here...
噢
Oh.
安娜
Ana.
那是羅冰遜夫人嗎
Was that Mrs. Robinson?
她名叫艾琳娜-林肯
Her name's Elena Lincoln.
我不在乎她叫什麼 克裡斯汀
I don't care what her name is, Christian.
你為什麼要帶我去那裡
Why would you take me there?
你為什麼要帶我去見那個誘惑並虐待過你的女人
Why would you take me to meet the woman who seduced and abused you?
我們的關係幾年前就結束了 我們現在只是朋友
Our relationship ended years ago. We're just friends.
兼合作夥伴
And business partners.
合作夥伴 你在逗我麼
Business partners? Are you kidding me?
你會帶你的女奴們去那裡
Would you take your subs there?
老天 為了什麼 她的認可
Oh, my god! For what? Her approval?
什麼 這是在幹嘛
What? What is this?
不 這是..不是這樣的
No. It's not like that.
我今早看到的那個女孩也是他們之一對麼？
That girl that I saw this morning was one of them, wasn't she?
我們去我家討論這個吧 我可以叫人來給你做髮型
Let's discuss this back at my place.
我可以叫人來給你做髮型
I can have someone come by, do your hair.
我不在乎我的髮型如何
Christian, I don't care about my hair!
給我解釋這到底是怎麼回事
Explain to me what's going on.
到我家我就給你解釋聽 來
I'll explain when we're there. Come on.
好吧 要不你自己走 要不我帶你走
Okay, you can either walk or i can carry you. Your choice.
你不會那麼做的 不 你自己選
You wouldn't do that. No, it's your choice.
好吧 好 好 我自己走
Okay, fine. Fine. I'll walk.
她叫利拉-威廉姆斯
Her name's Leila Williams.
大概兩年前我們交往過一段時間
She was my sub for a while about two years ago.
她發生了什麼
What happened to her?
她想要更多 而我不想了
She wanted more. I didn't.
所以我和她就分手了
So I ended it.
她離開了  和別人結了婚
She left. Got married.
我以為她會過得很好 但之後她丈夫出車禍死了
I thought she moved on, but then her husband died in a car crash.
她精神崩潰了
She had a breakdown.
她現在想幹什麼
What does she want now?
當我們一在喬治亞州的時候
When you and I were in Georgia together, she turned up here
她出現在我的管家瓊斯夫人面前想要割腕自殺
and tried to slit her wrists in front of Mrs. Jones, my housekeeper.
天啊
Oh, my god.
蓋爾送她去醫院但當我感到哪裡時
Gail took her to the hospital, but by the time I got there,
她已經走了
she'd taken off.
我的人一直試圖找到她
My people have been trying to find her.
你的人
Your people?
就是把資料收集在一起的人
Is that who put this together?
也有這樣的人在盯著我麼
Is there one on me?
讓我看看
Let me see it.
咪表在裡士滿大道的克萊德五金店打工
"Subject works part time at Clayton's hardware, Richmond road."
他們沒有算我上廁所的時間
You know, they didn't time my bathroom breaks.
你應該要求退款
You should probably get your money back.
我會讓他們接近任何潛在的受虐者
I had them drawn up on any prospective submissive.
很好 老天啊
Nice. Jesus.
我不知道這事會變成什麼樣
I had no idea what this was gonna become.
我不知道你會變得如此特殊
I didn't know you'd be different.
特殊？真的
Different? Really?
這就是你像帶所有你其他的女人那樣
Is that why you brought me to Mrs. Robinson's,
帶我去見羅賓遜夫人的原因  因為我非常特殊？
where you brought all the other women? Because I'm so different?
這是錯誤的 我承認
That was wrong. I admit.
這是完全錯誤的 這一切都是錯的
It's all wrong. All of this is wrong.
你匯錢到我的賬戶 我不想要你的錢
You put money into my account that... I don't want it.
你收購了我在職的公司
You bought the company i work for.
這不是戀愛關係克裡斯汀  這是從屬關係
This isn't a relationship, Christian. It's ownership.
我努力想要瞭解你
I'm trying to understand you.
我只是想接近你
Lam just wanting to get close to you.
不過當你像這樣一直作怪
But it's really difficult to do that when you keep doing
我真的很難做到這一點
bizarre things like this.
而且你不讓我碰你 也讓我很難接受你
And it's really difficult to do that when you won't let me touch you.
來我的臥室
Come to my bedroom.
性現在解決不聊這個問題  你瘋了麼
Sex is not gonna fix this right now. Are you insane?
安娜 求你
Ana, please.
你想要個路線圖
You wanted a road map?
從這開始
Start here.
這些是我的底線
Those are my boundaries.
這個我可以接受
I can live with that.
然後我就都是你的了
Then I'm all yours.
格雷先生你預約的客人到了
Woman". Mr. grey, your appointment's arrived.
好的帶她到安娜的房間
Okay. Send him into Ana's room.
他來了
He's here.
誰來了
Who's here?
哇
Wow.
讓頭髮蓬起來 好吧？
Hair up, I think. Yes?
你的脖子很美
Your neck is beautiful.
克裡斯汀
Christian?
Ciao, Bella.
你打算待在哪裡看麼
You're just gonna stand there gawking?
是的
Yeah.
是的這樣挺好
Yeah, I think I might.
所以我在想
So I was thinking
今晚可能會更刺激
tonight might be more stimulating
如果你穿這些。
if you wear these.
我該怎麼穿呢？
How am I supposed to wear those?
好吧
Well,
你必須先弄濕它們。
you have to get them wet first.
好奇嗎？
Curious?
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
好吧
Okay.
張開嘴
Open your mouth.
很好
Good.
現在 彎腰
Now turn. Bend over.
不，你不能把它放進我的屁股。
No, you're not putting those in my butt.
他們不進你的屁股。
They don't go in your butt.
別動
Stay still.
站直 然後轉身
Stand up straight and turn around.
感覺怎樣
How's it feel?
嗯
Mmm...
很奇怪
Weird.
還不錯
But good.
這是在幹什麼
What do they do?
你會知道的
You'll find out.
穿銀色禮服。
Wear the silver satin.
會很順利
It'll go well with these.
別擔心 他們是你的耳朵。
Don't worry. They're for your ears.
我說過這是一個假面舞會麼
Did I mention it was a masked ball?
沒有
No.
你的新保鏢也要帶上這些
Your new bodyguards need to wear these, too?
我只是要確保安全
I'm just being safe.
你甚至感覺不到他們存在
You won't even notice they're here.
走吧
Come on.
The way you wear your hat
the way you sip your tea
the memory of all that
no, no, they can't take that away from me
the way your smile just beams
the way you sing off-key
每個人都在看我們
everybody's looking at us.
不是我們  是你
Not us. You.
克裡斯汀 我很高興你趕來了 母親
Christian! I'm so glad you made it. Mother.
說實話 母親穿的真正式
"Mother" is so formal. Honestly.
安娜你好
Ana. Hi.
你最近如何
How you doing?
這些很漂亮 也很神秘
These things are beautiful, and they are mysterious,
不過他們也很煩人
but they're a pain in the ass.
你看起來美得驚人
You look spectacular.
謝謝 你也是這裙子 真漂亮
Thank you. So do you. This dress is so beautiful.
謝謝安娜
Thank you, Ana.
我很高興你回到克裡斯汀身邊
I'm so glad you're back with Christian.
失去你他就像迷路的孩子
He was lost without you.
我能要回我的女伴了麼
Oh. Can I have my date back, please?
當然可以  你可真掃興
By all means. Spoilsport.
待會見
See you later.
No, no, they can't take that away from me
安娜 我的天
Ana! My god!
這裙子 沒得沒邊兒了 莫尼克-魯裡耶
That dress, it should be illegal. Monique lhuillier.
是的 米亞
Yeah. Mia.
米亞 我差點認不出你
Mia, you know i barely recognized you.
是啊 這個嶄新的我 吧 你覺得怎麼樣
Yeah! The new me. Okay, what do you think?
非常的金髮碧眼
Well, it's very, uh, blonde.
你是怎麼忍受他的
How do you put up with him?
你知道青少年時期的他更讓人頭痛
Do you know he was an even bigger pain as a teenager?
它曾因為打架先後被4所學校開除
He got expelled from four different schools for brawling.
像個完全失控的野獸
That's enough. Yeah, totally out of control.
夠了 米亞 別說了 米亞？
- Mia, enough. - Mia?
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
嗨  你好麼
Hi! How are you?
安娜
H Mm? Ana?
你坐在這裡親愛的 緊挨著克裡
You will be sitting here, darling. Right next to Cary.
克裡斯汀 你在這裡
Christian, you over here.
女士們先生們 歡迎光臨我們的年度舞會
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to our annual ball.
正如你們所知 今晚的所有收益
As you know, proceeds from this evening
都將捐獻給格雷和我多年前創辦的
will go to the charity that grace and I founded so many years ago...
慈善機構
Coping together.
該組織致力於
Working to make life better for the children...
父母是癮君子的兒童提供更好的生活
of parents addicted to drugs.
你還好吧
Everything okay?
現在  我要滿懷感激的
And now, thankfully,
講話筒交給我們的主持人
I will be handing off my speaking duties
諾曼德-保羅 先生
to our master of ceremonies, Mr. nomad Paul.
謝謝 格雷先生  還有謝謝你們
Paul". Thank you, Mr. grey, and thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
餓了麼
Hungry?
現在從一號商品開始競價
Let's start the bidding with lot number one.
餓瘋了
Ravenous.
有人出價一萬美元嗎？
- Do I hear $10, 000? - Ten!
現在你知道這些銀球是幹什麼用的了
Now you know what those silver balls do.
一萬五千美元
Woman'. $15,000.
Paul'. $15,000.
一次  兩次
Going once, going twice...
成交
Sold!
這是個好的開始 女士們先生們 現在二號商品
That's a great start, ladies and gentlemen. Now, lot number two,
由克裡斯汀-格雷先生贊助的 位於科羅拉多州
a week's vacation at a luxury chalet in Aspen, Colorado,
阿斯本豪華度假小屋入住一星期
donated by Mr. Christian grey.
嗯..
Mmm.
低價一萬美金 開始競價
Let's start the bidding off at $10,000.
一萬美金
$10,000!
謝謝 女士 一萬美金
Thank you, ma'am. $10,000.
我怎麼不知道你在阿斯本還有房產
I didn't know you had a place in Aspen.
我有很多房產
I have a lot of places.
老天今晚 這裡有滑雪愛好者
Boy, we have some ski lovers in the room tonight.
一萬七千美金
$17,000!
一萬七千美金  謝謝
$17,000. Thank you, sir. 18?
一萬八千美金
$18,000. $18,000.
謝謝 一萬九美金？
Thank you. Do I hear 19? 19?
一萬九美金
19.
一萬九美金 謝謝先生
$19,000. Thank you, sir.
美國第一滑雪勝地的一周豪華之旅
A week of luxury in America's finest ski resort.
兩萬四千美金
$24,000.
新面孔  有人出到兩萬四千美金了
New blood! $24,000 I am bid.
有出價兩萬五千美金的嗎
Do I hear $25,000?
這錢是給你的
That money was for you.
現在這筆錢給需要它的人了
And now it'll go to someone who needs it.
我不知道是該跪下來膜拜你還是該打你屁股
I don't know whether to worship at your feet or spank you.
兩萬四千美金一次
$24, 000. Going once...
兩萬四千美金兩次
I think... Going twice...
我想我會選第二個
l'll take option two.
成交給這位穿銀禮服的年輕女士
Sold! To the young lady in silver.
你們的慷慨會帶來改變 女士們先生們
Your generosity really makes a difference, ladies and gentlemen.
我們走
Let's go.
你要這個？
You want this?
我要你打我
I want you to spank me.
手
Hands.
如果你受不了你可以喊我停下來 明白
If it gets too much, you have to tell me to stop, understood?
明白
Yes.
別動
Hold still.
這是你的房間
Ls this your room?
很久以前是
Once upon a time.
這是誰
Who's this?
是你母親
Is that your mother?
如果你不想談這個 你可以說
You know you can just say you don't wanna talk about it.
是 我不想談這個
Yeah, I don't wanna talk about it.
走吧 他們會找到我們的
Let's go. They'll be missing us.
我還需要在準備一下
Uh, I just need a minute.
我們樓下見
I'll meet you downstairs.
好吧
Okay.
別忘了你的面具
Don't forget your mask.
under my skin
I'd sacrifice anything come what might
for the sake of having you near
什麼
what?
沒什麼
Nothing.
comes in the night and repeats and repeats in my ear
don't you know, little fool you never can win
克裡斯汀有伴了
Christian has a date.
了不起
I'm impressed.
抱歉
I'm sorry?
安娜
Elena.
我本想去見你來著
I wanted to meet you.
我毫無興趣 抱歉失陪了
I can't say the same. Excuse me.
嘿 我不是你的敵人
Hey, I'm not the enemy.
我知道你對克裡斯汀做了什麼
I know what you did to Christian.
我所做的一切都是在引導他 找到真實的自己
All I did was lead him to the truth of who he really is.
沒有我 他 早進監獄或死了
Without me, he'd be in jail or dead.
他也是這樣認為的
And he would say the same.
我不想聽這種話
I'm not listening to this.
你覺得你是第一個 他希望能狗拯救自己的女人麼
Do you think you're the first woman he'd hoped would save him?
他的生活需要一個受虐者
He needs a submissive in life.
不只是在床上的那種
Not "gust 'm the bedroom.
不 他正在改變這一點
No, he's changing that.
這不再是他想到的了
It's not what he wants anymore.
但這是他所需要的
But it's what he needs.
而我覺得你斌不是那種她想要擁有的女人
And you don't strike me as the type of woman who wants to be owned.
如果你真的想要讓他幸福 如果你想要幸福
If you really wanna make him happy, if you wanna be happy,
你該離開他
you'll let him go.
想你這種人  是不可能理解我們的感情的
There's no way that someone like you could ever understand what we have.
我曾和你一樣
I've been there.
沒有什麼能夠天長地久
Nothing lasts.
沒有
Nothing.
我和克裡斯汀之間的一切
Whatever happens between me and Christian
都不關你的事
is none of your goddamn business.
你離我們遠點
So you stay the fuck away from us.
嘿，我們改考慮退場了
Hey, we should think about going soon.
我現在就想走
I wanna go now.
艾琳娜 隊你說什麼了
What did Elena say to you?
沒什麼新鮮的
Nothing I didn't already know.
你能把我送回我家麼
Will you just take me to my house?
今晚留下來陪我吧
Stay with me tonight.
嘿 醒醒 我們到家了
Hey, wake up. We're home. Hmm.
先生
Sir?
你待在這
Stay here.
我們會找人來拖車的
We'll have the car towed.
怎麼了
What happened?
那是我的車 我的車怎麼了
That's my car! What happened to my car?
搜索房間 然後確定安全給我打電話
Check the apartment. Call me when it's safe.
是 先生 馬上就去
Yes, sir. Right away. Copy that.
史密斯 你跟著格雷先生
Smith, you stick with Mr. grey.
我們要去那兒
Where are we going?
克裡斯汀
Christian?
你覺得是利拉麼
Do you think it was Leila?
你真的覺的她會做這種事
You really think she would do something like that?
我不明白為什麼我們不能回你家
I really don't see why we can't just go back to your apartment.
那個房子像個碉堡
That place is like a fortress.
她不可能進的去
There's no way she could have gotten in there.
她也不該能進的去車庫
She shouldn't have been able to get into the garage, either.
我不能冒一點風險
I'm not taking any chances.
晚上好格雷先生
Good evening, Mr. grey.
嗨 艾德
Hey, ed.
剩下的人早上到
The rest of the crew will be here in the morning.
如果你因為我而出事
If something were to happen to you because of me...
不會的
It won't.
我不會出事的
Nothing's gonna happen to me.
我幫你洗吧
Can I wash this off?
不要偏離線條。
Don't stray from the lines.
好吧
Okay.
這是燒傷麼
Are these burns?
這是誰幹得
Who did this to you?
繼續吧 已經過去了
Go on, it's over.
我知道向我敞開心扉
I know how difficult it is for you to open up to me
告訴我你的過去 對你來說有多困難
and tell me these things.
不過這對我來說就是一切
But it means the world to me.
這意味著你愛我
It means you love me.
是的 我愛你
Yes, I do.
所以你的打結技術就是這麼來的
So this is where your knot-tying expertise comes from.
早上好
Good morning.
你睡得好麼
Sleep well?
是的
I did.
這船很漂亮
This boat is really beautiful.
這出自於我在寫西雅圖造船廠
This is from my yard in Seattle.
你建造的？
You built it?
在一些人的幫助下
I had some help.
它叫 格蕾絲號
It's called the grace.
以你母親的名字命名的？
After your mom?
你聽起來很驚訝
You sound surprised.
你總是對她很冷淡而且
Well, you're always so cool towards her.
格蕾絲給了我一切
I owe everything to grace.
她在我生母死後拯救了我
She saved my life after my birth mom died.
你還記得你的生母嗎？
Do you remember your birth mom?
我嘗試去忘記她
I try not to.
她怎麼了？
What happened to her?
她吸毒過度而死
She overdosed.
她的屍體三天後被發現
They found her body three days later.
當時你在哪裡
Where were you?
我在她身邊
I was with her.
哦 我的天
Oh, my god.
人們帶走了她 帶我去了醫院
Took her away. Took me to a hospital.
格蕾絲在哪
Grace was there.
謝謝你告訴我這些
Thank you for telling me.
看看你那棟房子
Look at that house.
真美 房子的儘管肯定很漂亮
That's beautiful. The view's probably amazing.
真想知道誰會住在哪裡
I wonder who lives there.
是個海軍的老遺孀
It's an old sea widow.
幾年前他的丈夫過世了
Lost her husband years ago.
從此她每晚坐在窗前 等待他回家
Sits at the window every night waiting for him to come home.
這故事是你自己編的麼
Did you just make that up?
是的
Yeah.
你想把船開回家麼
You wanna take the helm?
我
Me'?
是的 你   來吧
Yeah, you. Come on.
我不會開的
I can't do that.
看到我指的那裡了嗎？ 是的
See where I'm looking? Yeah.
就是哪裡抓住了
Right there. Just hold.
好嗎 好的
Okay? Okay,
不 你沒事 安娜 我還在這裡
no, you're fine, Ana. I'm still here.
別放手
Don't let go.
好吧 我不得不放手了
I have to let go. Don't.
別 天啊
Oh, my god. Okay. Okay?
你準備好了 是的
You ready? Okay.
老天 老天 我的老天 我在開船
Oh, my god! Oh, my god! I'm steering it.
我在開船 我是船長
I'm doing it. I'm the captain.
哦 我的天
Oh, my god!
嘿 嘿 傑克
Hey. Hey, Jack.
私人電話私人時間再打 好吧
Personal calls on your own time, okay?
好
Yeah?
什麼事 你收到我的信息了嗎？
Um, did you get my message?
你本來今天上午九點要給露絲-卡露絲打電話的
You had a phone call this morning with Ruth carusi at 9:00 A.M.
該死
Shit.
我在找時間 我會問他們的
I can just reschedule it. I'll ask them.
你定好我們去紐約的房間了嗎？
Did you book our rooms for New York yet?
抱歉
Sorry?
紐約 書展 這週五 在你的日誌裡記著的
New York. Book expo. This Friday. It's in the diary.
是的  我定好你的房間了 當然
No, yeah, I know. Yeah, i booked your room. Of course.
還有你
And you.
按計劃我的助理也要出席
It's expected that my assistant also attends.
我不知道這是 抱歉
I didn't know that. I'm sorry.
別道歉
Don't apologize.
給你自己也訂個房間
Just get yourself a room.
除非你更願意留下來陪你男朋友
Unless you'd rather stay back with your boyfriend.
畢竟你看起來不需要工作
I mean, it's not like you need to work.
(Jack clears throat';
我會處理好的
I'll sort it out.
埃裡克 嘿 我是傑克 週末過的怎麼樣
Eric, hey. It's Jack. How was your weekend?
不是吧
No shit.
我的週末很好 棒極了
Mine was great. It was fantastic.
嗯 因為我讀了你的新文章
Yeah, 'cause I read your new pages.
不  寫的很棒 非常精彩
No, they're amazing. Amazing.
不 我讀的都停不下來
No, I couldn't put it down.
我們會的到州和聯邦的政府補助
We'll be accessing state and federal grants of course,
不過超過七成的資金將來自
but more than 70% of the funding...
格雷控股集團
will come directly from grey enterprises holdings.
我這週末要去紐約
我們將製造可再生能源科技
We'll be making cutting edge renewable energy tech
這受益要大大超過我們的投資
that will more than repay our investment.
和你上司？
為了工作 我需要去紐約
答案是 不准去
我不是在問你的意見
可以提供堅實的消費者基礎
provides a solid consumer base...
為我們的產品。
for our products.
我們知道您有其他投標人
We're aware that you have other bidders
其中一些可能會提供什麼看起來更好的條件，但...
and some of them may offer what look like better terms, but...
我們回頭再談
哈嘍
Hello?
克裡斯汀
Christian?
哦 我的天
Oh, my god!
抱歉 斯蒂爾女士 我沒想嚇著你
Oh, excuse me, miss Steele, i didn't mean to startle you.
不 沒事
No, no.
你挺安靜的
You are very quiet.
我是瓊斯夫人 格雷先生的管家 我來吧
I'm Mrs. Jones. Mr. grey's housekeeper. May I?
哦 嗯
Oh, um...
當然  謝謝
Sure. Thank you.
我是安娜
Um, I'm Ana.
我已經知道你的名字了 你剛剛叫了我的姓
But you knew that already because you said my last name.
格雷先生在瑞安的書房裡 他剛打完一通電話
Mr. grey is in his study, just finishing up a call.
如果你需要我 我就在廚房裡  好的
I'll be in the kitchen if you need me. Okay.
看到你喜歡的東西了嗎
See anything you like?
真是的
Oh, fuck.
門沒鎖
The door was, um, unlocked.
我得和瓊斯夫人聊聊
I'll have to talk to Mrs. Jones.
她經常進來裡？
Does she come in here a lot?
比如 來這裡打掃？
Does she dust in here?
那些是乳頭夾
Those are nipple clamps.
過來 把你的手給我
Come here. Give me your hand.
打你拿掉它們的時候感覺比夾著的時候更疼
It's even more intense when you take them off.
哇哦
Ow.
這是什麼？
What's this?
好吧
Okay.
示範夠了
That's enough show-and-tell.
這是什麼？
What's this?
欲速則不達
Let's learn to walk before we run.
我還挺喜歡速度的
I kinda like running.
安娜
Ana? Mmm-hmm?
我們上回做這事的時候  你看到我的另一面
Last time we did this, you saw another side of me.
然後你離開了我
And you left.
上回情況不一樣
Last time was different.
好吧 但不是在這裡
All right. But not here.
瓊斯夫人
Mrs. Jones.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
你是我的
You're mine.
我是你的。
I'm yours.
你還好麼?  很好
You okay? Yeah.
你知道我們總得談談去紐約的事
You know at some point we're gonna need to talk about New York.
我們已經談過了
We have talked about it.
你禁止我去不等於我們談過了
You forbidding it is not us talking about it.
如果你想去紐約別和海德一起去
If you wanna go to new York, don't go with Hyde.
讓我帶你去 我在紐約有房產
Let me take you. I have a place there.
你當然有
Of course you do.
這可不是度假
This isn't some sort of vacation.
這是跟我老闆出差 我還想給他留些好印象呢
It's a work trip with my boss, who I would like to impress.
你知道在過去的十八個月裡 他換了三個助理
You know he's had three assistants in the last 18 months,
他們三個都匆匆辭職了
all of whom have quit without notice?
你覺得我搞不定他？
You don't think i can handle him?
不是這樣的
That's not it.
給我的感覺就是這樣
That's what it feels like.
安娜 我非常清楚你能搞定任何事
Ana, I know full well that you can handle anything.
我也知道如果你真想去
And, uh, if you really wanna go,
我阻止不了你
then I can't stop you.
不過我想親自帶你去
But I'd like to take you there myself.
好吧
Okay.
好嗎？
Okay?
好的
Yeah.
我是說  我當然更願意和你一起去看看紐約
I mean, of course I would rather see New York with you.
很好
Good.
我討厭我們吵架
I hate it when we fight.
剛才那不是吵架
That wasn't a fight.
那是對話
That was a conversation.
那是一個人講話另一個人聽
It was, you know, when somebody talks, and the other person listens,
然後解決問題
and you resolve an issue.
這就是相處之道
That's how it works.
很瘋狂 不是嗎？
It's crazy, isn't it?
晚安 安娜
Night, Ana.
晚安 漢娜
Good night, Hannah.
一起吃晚飯?
兩分鐘後見
你要走了?
You leaving?
我過來就是想和你談談 關於去紐約的事
Um, I was actually just about to come talk to you. Uh, about New York.
有問題嗎?
There a problem?
嗯
Um...
我很感激你給我的這次機會 傑克
I'm so grateful for the opportunity, Jack,
但通知太倉促了 我有其他安排
but with such short notice, i made plans
也不能更改
that I can't change. Huh.
不過我整個週末都會帶著手機
But I will have my phone on me all weekend.
如果你需要我做什麼 我隨時執行
So if you need anything, I'm available.
安娜 請坐
Ana, have a seat.
我真的 很抱歉
I'm really... I'm sorry.
我認為你在這份工作上有很大的潛力
I think you have tremendous potential here.
但我不想浪費時間去培訓
But I don't wanna waste my time
一個不認真對待這份工作的人
training someone who doesn't take this position seriously.
我很認真
I do.
這是我夢寐以求的工作
This is my dream job.
那就去紐約 參加書展不該麼 是這個夢想的一部分嗎?
Then shouldn't going to New York and the book expo be part of that dream?
那只是一部分
It is.
那是
之前是我沒搞清楚狀況 不會再次發生了
It was just a misunderstanding. It won't happen again.
外面有很多又能力的人 他們會為這份工作爭破頭
Because there are plenty of qualified people who would kill for this job.
我的意思是 我不想吹牛 我是一個很好的老師
I mean, look, I don't wanna brag, but I'm a pretty great teacher.
我確定你是如此
I'm sure you are.
我只是沒看出來你有什麼進取心
I'm just not seeing the initiative on your side of it.
除了你的要求  我還讀了很多
I've read more than you've asked me to.
我可以說是讀了所有的
And I'm on top of everything...
我說的是更上一層樓
I'm talking about going the extra mile.
除非你希望
Unless you want me
我跟克裡斯汀
to compete with Christian grey
爭風吃醋
for your attention.
那天克裡斯汀對你很無禮 我替他向你道歉
I apologize that Christian was so curt with you the other night.
你就是在糾結這個嗎?
Is that what this is about?
你男朋友向來以
Your boyfriend has a reputation for being
冷酷無情著稱
a little ruthless.
你喜歡這種男人?
Is that what you like?
如果你對我的工作不滿意  那你應該去找人事部
If you have a problem with my work, then you should take it up with hr.
哇哦
Whoa.
你這麼認真幹嘛
Why are you being so serious?
你以為我會怎麼做? 讓你上我
What do you think I'm gonna do? Make you fuck me?
傑克
Jack.
我只是
I just think...
覺得
I just think
我只是覺得如果你打算靠出賣肉體爬上去
if you're gonna fuck your way to prominence,
最起碼你得找個能拉高你智商的人
then you should do it with someone who can at least make you smarter.
而不只是讓你更有錢而已
Not just richer.
對嗎?
Right?
別 別怎麼?
Don't... Don't what? Hmm?
聽著 這是個非常嚴肅的問題
Look, this is a serious, serious question.
你是想被無視
Do you wanna be kept
還是被當回事兒
or taken seriously? Hmm?
我想離開這裡 求你了 傑克
I would like to leave, please, Jack.
還有
Plus...
我能讓你高潮 給你其他人無法給你的體驗
Loan make you come like nobody else has.
他給不了你的
Not him.
誰都給不了你
Not anyone.
不
No.
安娜? 安娜 出什麼事了?
Ana? Ana, what happened?
傑克-海德 傑克對我欲行不軌
Jack Hyde tried to touch me.
我要殺了他
I'll kill him.
不要 求你了  別去
No, no, please don't go. Don't go. Don't leave me.
別離開我
Okay. Go.
好的 走吧 沒事了
It's okay. Hey...
我把東西都丟那了 什麼也沒拿
I left everything. I don't have any of my stuff.
泰勒會拿過來的 沒事了 好嗎
Taylor will get it. It's fine, okay?
我送你回家 走吧
I'll take you home, come on.
他的門禁證件被吊銷了?
And his pass has been cancelled?
很好
Good.
不 謝謝你 傑瑞 晚安
No. Thank you, Jerry. Good night.
至少那件事已經處理好了
Well, at least that's dealt with.
海德出局了  他被炒了
Hyde's out. He's been fired.
哇哦
Whoa.
怎麼會 真是
How? That's...
我以為你跟sip的生意還沒完成
But I thought your deal with sip hasn't been finished yet.
是的 我認識他們的執行總裁
It's not. But I know the ceo.
我把事情都告訴了他
I told him what happened.
你以後再也看不到他了
You'll never have to see him again.
既然他已經離開 那我還能在那工作嗎?
Am I still gonna have a job now that he's not there?
要是你工作沒了 你就乾脆
Well, if you don't, you can just...
克裡斯汀 你知道我喜歡工作
Christian, you know i love working.
你不能把我一直關在你加閣樓裡
You can't keep me locked up in your penthouse.
我給你鑰匙如何
What if I gave you a key?
我是說
I mean,
我給你一把這裡的鑰匙 你可以把一些東西放這
what if you had a key, and you kept some of your stuff here?
你可以吧所有東西都放這兒
Keep all of your stuff here and you slept, you know...
不用回你住的地方
Not at your place.
你這是讓我搬過來和你一起住?
Are you asking me to move in with you?
是的
Mmm-hmm.
你確定嗎?
Are you sure?
確定
Yes.
我希望你一直都在這兒
I want you here all the time.
希望你盡快搬進來
As soon as possible.
你之前不是說欲速則不達嗎?
What happened to learning to walk before we run?
這個麼 這是事我們眾多早餐話題中的一個
That's just one of the many things that we could talk about over breakfast.
我能考慮下嗎?
Can I think about it?
當然可以
Sure.
好的
Yeah.
莉茲 嗨
Liz, hi!
安娜 不知你是否聽說 傑克昨晚辭職了
Ana, don't know if you heard, but Jack resigned last night.
走得匆匆忙忙的
In kind of a hurry.
sip 現在不招新人 咱倆快完蛋了
Sip isn't recruiting right now, so we're screwed.
這麼說 你不需要我了 對嗎?
So you don't need me anymore then?
我們會給你安排個臨時工作
I'm gonna try to find you something temporary.
今天早上你能先補下傑克的空嗎?
Could you fill in for Jack at this morning's meeting?
高級編輯會議?
At the senior editors' meeting?
就今天而已
Just for today.
只有你清楚傑克的工作
You're the only one who knows Jack's entire slate.
是的 可 我
Well, yeah, but, I...
你說的對  這個要求確實有點過分
You're right. It's too much.
不 我能行
No, I can do it.
沒關係 我可以的
It's fine. I can do it.
很好
Great.
散會了給我打電話
Call me when you're done.
我們應該精簡發行作品
We need to print fewer titles.
只跟有名氣的作家約稿
Stick with established authors.
關注我們的核心讀者
Focus on our core readership.
擴大核心讀者群
Expand it.
什麼?
I'm sorry?
那你覺得我們應該出版什麼樣的作品
Um, uh... so, Ana, what do you think we should be publishing?
新鮮的血液
Um, newer voices.
還有你那些有名氣的作家
Along with your established authors. Mmm-hmm.
比如 博伊斯-福克斯 他的文章上周獲得80萬點擊量
Boyce fox, for example, got 80,000 hits last week.
真的嗎?
Really?
線上點擊不一定能促進紙媒銷量
Online hits don't automatically translate to print sales.
但它們可以
Well, but they could.
從人口統計血的角度看 他的線上讀者年齡處於18-24之間
His online audience is an 18-to-24 demographic,
而這些人正是我們需要爭取的讀者群體
and those are exactly the readers that we should be chasing.
我可以給你們看下數據 我覺得他值得我們冒險
Um, I mean, I can show you the stats. I think he's worth taking a risk on.
也許我們該看看統計數字
Maybe we should take a look.
這個主意很好
Great idea.
安娜? 安娜 稍等
Uh, Ana? Ana, just...
洛奇先生 如果我剛才越界了 我真的很抱歉
Mr. roach, I'm really sorry if I was out of line.
不 沒關係 你說的很有道理
No, don't be sorry. You made a lot of sense.
不 傑克-海德都走了 你還在這兒幹嘛
No, so, uh, what are you doing now that Jack Hyde's gone?
莉茲說給我安排個臨時工作
Urn, well, Liz mentioned something temporary. I don't know.
好的 那你為何不暫時頂替傑克的位置
Okay. So why don't you fill in for Jack temporarily?
行麼?
Good? Um...
太好了 沒問題 就這麼定了
Great. Okay. That's settled.
為sip 新任小說編輯乾杯
To sip's new fiction editor.
代理小說編輯
Acting fiction editor.
他們遲早會知道你有多優秀
Till they find out how good you are.
這事兒沒動用你的關係嗎?
Christian, did you have something to do with this?
沒有 這都是你自己的努力得來的
No. Hey, it was all you.
怎麼 你不相信我
What? You don't believe me?
我是不相信自己
I don't believe it myself.
我昨晚問了你的問題
I asked you a question last night.
你說搬過來和你一起住的事?
About moving in with you? Mmm-hmm.
我只是覺得自己可能
I just think that I'm probably...
我需要從自己住的地方拿點東西
I need to get some things from my apartment.
我可以安排
That can be arranged.
好的
Good.
也許我們可以
Now, maybe we could
回家慶祝一番
take this celebration home. 服務員 結賬
服務員 結賬
The check, please.
脫掉你的內褲
Take off your panties.
現在就做
Do it now. 在這裡嗎?
在這裡嗎?
Right in here?
是的,在這裡。現在。
Yeah, right here. Now.
繼續。
Go on.
Hmm.
抱歉。
Excuse me.
不來了。
Don't come.
Mmm-mmm. Mmm-mmm. No.
兩分鐘。 你在開玩笑嗎?
Two minutes. Are you kidding?
在臥室。你開玩笑嗎?
In the bedroom. Are you joking?
兩分鐘的時間。
Two minutes.
你這是要幹什麼?
What are you doing in here?
你讓我等的
You made me wait,
所以現在該輪到你了
so now it's your turn.
你行嗎
Are you any good?
走著瞧
Hmm. We'll see.
或許我們應該打個賭。
Maybe we should make a bet.
如果我贏
If I win,
你帶我去紅房子。
you take me to the red room.
如果我贏了
And if I win?
你可以選
Your choice.
開始
Break.
好吧
Okay.
嗯. 全色
Mmm. Solids.
哦，親愛。
Oh, dear.
側袋
Side pocket.
紅房間，我們來了。
Red room, here we come.
Oof.
該死
Shit.
我希望你不是一個痛苦的輸家
I hope you're not a sore loser.
這取決於你如何努力打我屁股。
That depends on how hard you spank me.
我非常想粗暴的對你
I want to be very rough with you.
所以對我粗暴吧
So be rough with me.
捷達需要人在新版科魯茲上簽字
And Jada needs someone to sign off on the new carusi.
我一直讓傑克去簽
I kept asking Jack to do that.
是啊 但傑克有點懶
Yeah, well, Jack was kind of lazy.
你沒注意到嗎?
Didn't you notice?
注意到了
Yeah.
他把這叫做 藝術氣質
I believe he called it "artistic temperament."
謝了 漢娜
Thank you, Hannah.
不客氣
Yep.
嗨
Hey,
你能來做這項工作很棒
it's great that you're doing this, but...
但這樣 感覺很奇怪 我懂
It's totally weird, i know. I know.
我是不是該稱呼你斯蒂爾女士
I mean, am I expected to call you miss Steele?
還是叫我安娜吧
I expect you to call me Ana.
除非你也需要
And I don't expect you to fetch me coffee
否則不用專門去幫我倒咖啡
unless you're getting some for yourself.
至於其他的事情 我們慢慢磨合吧  好嗎?
And the rest of it, we'll just make up as we go, okay?
好的
Okay.
斯蒂爾女士
Miss Steele.
該死
Damn it.
接吧 我去拿點東西 查下郵箱
Take it. I'm just gonna grab some stuff and check the mail.
我跟你一起上去
I should go up with you.
不沒事的 我馬上回來
No, it's okay. I'll be two seconds.
接吧
Take it.
嗨  羅斯
Hey, ros.
利拉
Leila.
克裡斯汀在樓下
Christian is downstairs.
你想要見他嗎?
Do you wanna see him?
我是來找你的
I came to see you.
好吧
Okay.
他都告訴我了
He told me what happened.
我知道你現在很痛苦
I know you're in a lot of pain.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
他允許你叫他的名字
He lets you call him by his name.
他總談起你
He talks about you all the time.
他在乎你
He cares about you.
別說謊了
Don't lie.
你到底那點比我好
Tell me what you have that I don't.
我哪點都不如你
Nothing.
我根本不算什麼
I'm nothing.
他遲早會厭倦我的
He'll get tired of me.
主人都睡到你床上了
Master sleeps in your bed.
你怎麼知道? 我看到你了
How do you know that? I saw you.
我一直在觀察你
I watched you.
我知道你愛他
I know you love him.
我也愛他
I do, too.
我們都愛他
We all do.
那你為何不把槍放下?
Why don't you put the gun down?
你不瞭解他 不知道他的喜好
You don't know him or what he likes.
他想要的你給不了 他跟你不過是逢場作戲
You don't give him what he wants. He's pretending with you.
不 克裡斯汀
No, Christian.
跪下
Kneel.
安娜
Ana...
去艾斯卡拉大廈等我
Go to escala. Wait for me there.
就聽我一次行不行
For once, just do as you're told.
泰勒 讓她出去
Taylor, get her out of here.
斯蒂爾女士
Miss Steele.
斯蒂爾女士 安娜
Miss Steele. Ana!
得了 泰勒
Stop it, Taylor.
我不管
I don't care.
她走了三小時了手機錢包都沒帶
She's been gone for three hours, and she doesn't have her cell or her purse.
算了 她回來了
Forget it. She's here.
你到底去哪兒了
Where the fuck have you been?
我讓你直接來著
I told you to come straight here.
我怕派人四處去找你
I've had people out combing the streets, looking for you.
抱歉我並不總是那麼聽話
I'm sorry I don't always do as I'm told.
也許你真的只是需要一個完全服從你的人
Maybe you just really need someone who obeys every command.
無風不起浪
Don't be ridiculous.
我看到你了 克裡斯汀
I saw you, Christian.
我看到你是如何對待利拉的
I saw the way you were with Leila.
她當時有槍 安娜
She had a gun, Ana.
為了制服她 我沒得選
I would have done anything to subdue her.
她現在在哪兒
Where is she now?
在這嗎?
Is she here?
什麼?
What?
不 當然不在
No, of course not.
她在精神病院裡接受治療
She's in the psych ward getting the help that she needs.
聽著 我知道她嚇著你了
Look, I know she scared you...
沒錯 她是把我嚇找了
Yeah. She scared me.
但你更讓我可怕
But you scared me more.
看你對她那樣
Seeing you like that with her.
我永遠做不到對你卑躬屈膝 言聽計從
I'll never be able to give you that kind of submission and obedience.
安娜
Ana.
別過來 我需要空間
Don't crowd me. I need space.
安娜 求你了別這樣 克裡斯汀
No, please don't do this. Christian.
別放棄我  我只是需要想想
Don't give up on me. I just need to think a little bit.
別離開我
Don't leave me.
你這是幹嘛
What are you doing?
起來
Get up.
你這是幹嘛
What are you doing?
看著我
Look at me.
我被嚇壞了
I'm scared.
我知道你會說有我在就足夠了
I know you say that I'm enough.
但以前你習慣得到的一些東西
But there are certain things that you are used to getting
我是永遠給不了的
that I will never, ever, ever be able to give you.
也許目前我們相處沒問題
And it might be fine for right now,
但萬一你又有那些需要的時候這麼辦
but what's gonna happen when you start needing them again?
不會的
I won't.
你怎麼知道
How do you know that?
我如何能相信你
How can I believe you?
我都不理解你為什麼總想支配別人
I don't even understand your need to dominate.
我不是要支配別人
I'm not a dominant.
我不是
I'm not.
確切的說我是個施虐狂
The right term is a sadist.
對女人的施虐能給我帶來快感 像你這樣的女人
I get off on punishing women. Women who look like you...
像你母親那樣的女人
Like your mother.
是的
Yes.
我知道自己有多變態
And I know how fucked up that is.
你走之後
When you left,
我發誓如果你能回來 我就不再施虐
I swore that I would stop it if that's what it took to get you back.
我再也不會那樣做了
But I'm done with it.
你是我生命裡最重要的人
You mean more to me than anything else.
我想相信你 真的
I wanna believe you. I do.
可我做不到
But I can't.
安娜 給我你的手
Ana, give me your hand.
這就是我
This is me.
所有的我
All of me.
克裡斯汀
Christian.
我全心全意愛你
And I'm all yours.
不
No.
不要
No!
嘿  沒事的
Hey. Hey, hey. No.
我在這
It's okay. I'm right here.
我在這呢
I'm right here.
嫁給我
Marry me.
什麼
What?
我想要娶你
I want you to marry me.
克裡斯汀 我覺得你是在做夢
Christian, I think you're dreaming.
早上好
Good morning.
早安
Morning.
睡得好麼
Sleep okay?
還不錯 你呢
I did. You?
睡得很沉  整晚都沒醒
Like a log. Out all night.
Hmm.
你沒做奇怪的夢嗎?
You didn't have any weird dreams or anything?
然後醒來什麼的
Or, like, wake up at all?
沒有
No.
我完全想不起來
I mean, none that I can think of.
嗯
Hmm.
有件小事  我好像跟你說了嫁給我
I mean, there was a little thing of asking you to marry me,
但除此之外什麼事都沒有
but aside from that, no. Nothing.
別這樣耍我
Don't mess with me like that.
不要嗎?  那我要怎樣耍你
No? How should i mess with you?
像這樣
Like this? Huh?
這樣好點麼
Ls that better?
我認真的
I meant it.
我想娶你
I wanna marry you.
為什麼
Why?
我想餘生每分每秒都能與你廝守
Because I wanna spend every second of the rest of my life with you.
我並不期待你馬上同意
I don't expect you to say yes right away.
我知道我這個人很複雜
I know I'm complicated.
有那麼一點而已
Just a little bit.
你有助手嗎?
You have an assistant?
我還以為你就是助手
I thought you were an assistant.
說來話長 有什麼事嗎?
It's a long story. What's going on?
我該給克裡斯汀買什麼生日禮物
What do I get Christian for his birthday?
這傢伙除了幽默感外什麼都不缺
The boy already has everything except a sense of humor.
他的
Uh...
他的生日?  什麼時候
His birthday? When is his birthday?
週日 他沒告訴你罵? 太奇怪了
Sunday. He didn't tell you? He is so weird.
爸媽要給他辦個派對
Mom and dad are throwing him a party.
他們不是剛辦過嗎?
Didn't they just have a party?
你和他一樣差勁 那是個舞會
Jeez, you're as bad as he is.
生日派對
That was a ball.
只有家人 朋友 音樂 煙花
This is just family, friends, music, fireworks.
沒什麼大不了的 賣個領帶怎麼樣
No biggie. Hey, what about a tie?
Uh, uh...
克裡斯汀的領帶多的是
Christian has a lot of ties.
襪子 褲子背帶 給點主意吧
Socks, suspenders? Throw me a bone here?
Um, oh...
天啊 米亞 我的走了
God, Mia, I gotta go.
好吧 但週末你必須來 不然我親自來把你抓過去
Okay, okay. But Sunday, or I'll hunt you down myself. Bye.
好極了
Ooh, perfect.
有禮物盒嗎?
Do you have a gift box?
稍等
One second.
嗨
Hey.
斯蒂爾女士
Miss Steele. Hmm.
今天過得好嗎?
How was your day?
還不錯 格雷先生
Looking up, Mr. grey.
泰勒去哪了
Where's Taylor?
他去那我的行李了
He went to get my bag.
你的行李  你要去哪
Your bag? Where are you going?
我和羅斯去波特蘭開會
Ros and I have to go to Portland for some meetings.
我明晚回來
I'll be back tomorrow night.
走吧
Come on.
你打算什麼時候告訴我你生日的事?
When were you going to tell me about your birthday?
你父母要給你辦派對
Your parents are throwing you a party.
難道我們就待在家裡嗎?
Were we just gonna stay home?
他們年年如此
They do this every year.
是啊 這可是生日
Um, yeah. Birthday.
我並不覺得我的降生是件值得慶祝的事
My, uh, arrival in the world isn't something I feel like celebrating.
我倒是覺得該慶祝一番
Well, I feel like celebrating it.
誕生日前不得打開
Can't open it till the day though.
那你為什麼現在給我
Then why give it to me now?
這叫做滿足感延遲
Call it delayed gratification.
沒有 你波特蘭的天空都是陰沉的
我也想你
你現在可以給我答案了嗎?
格雷先生 你可真固執
斯蒂爾女士 這可不是拒絕
明天約凱特出來喝一杯
別喝多了
我愛你晚安
聖海倫火山嗎?
Ls that... Ls that mount St. helens?
我改了計劃,會早點回來。
I changed the flight plan, get us home sooner.
太好了 你知道到這是一個火山,對吧?
Great. You realize that's a volcano, right?
放鬆 羅斯 如果它爆發，您將有一個首觀察席位
Relax, ros. If it goes up, you'll have a ringside seat.
Ah.
保佑我
Lucky me.
克裡斯汀 這是怎麼回事
Christian, what is that?
不用擔心
Don't worry.
哦 天啊 克裡斯汀
Oh, my god! Christian!
該死
Shit.
該死 克莉詩汀 什麼情況
Shit. Christian, what is going on?
求救 求救
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! What is happening?
停下 哦 天啊
Damn it. Oh, my god.
哦 我的天 克裡斯汀
Oh, my god, Christian!
停下
Stop it!
克裡斯汀
Christian!
那兒  那兒
There. There, there, there, there!
你記得這傢伙吧?
Oh, you remember this guy?
和那誰 凱特
Anastasiai Kate!
Hi!
哦 天啊 你氣色真好
Oh, my god! You're so tan and glowy.
安娜 要來瓶啤酒嗎?
You want a beer, Ana?
嗯 太好了
Yes! Please. Please.
嗨  何塞
Hi, Jose. Hey.
嗨 還好麼?
Hi! How's it going?
還用說嗎? 恭喜啊 小說編輯
So? Congratulations, fiction editor.
對吧 她現在可是大人物了
Right? She's a big deal now.
你那位怎麼樣了
And how's, uh, your hottie?
克裡斯汀還好
Uh, Christian is good.
Um, uh...
他要和我同居
He asked me to move in with him.
什麼
What?
安娜要跟克裡斯汀住一起了
Ana's moving in with Christian.
哦 那太好了
Oh, that's great.
我們能有點私人空間還真不錯呢
You know, we could use the privacy.
他太敏感了  簡直要了我的命
He's so subtle, it kills me.
打住
Stop.
所以你是認真的 但你開心嗎?
So you're serious. But are you happy?
因為我只關心這一件事
'Cause that's all I care about.
嗯 這很複雜 但我 從未如此快樂
I mean, it's complicated, but I've never been happier.
嘿 米亞 有什麼事
Hey, Mia, what's up?
你知道何塞上節目的事嗎?
Did you hear about Jose's show? It was incredible.
那簡直太棒了 真的 他真的很棒
Really. He was amazing.
他簡直好評如潮  我的去看看
He got rave reviews. I gotta check it out.
米亞 慢慢說
Wait, wait, Mia. Slow down.
該死的 好 我們這就到
Shit. Okay. Yeah, yeah, we're on our way.
克裡斯汀的直升機 在波特蘭返途失聯
Um, Christian's chopper went missing on the way back from Portland.
他們現在已經派出搜索隊
They're sending out search parties right now.
我們走
Come on, let's go.
關於此次突發事件的更多消息  讓我們
For more on this breaking story, let's go out to the field
連線場外記者 瑞秋-泰勒
and our reporter, Rachel Taylor.
瑞秋 謝謝約翰
Rachel? Thank you, John.
現在由我從私人直升機機場給你帶來現場報道
I'm speaking to you live from the private helicopter terminal at Seattle...
他們會找到他的 他會沒事的 他可是克裡斯汀
They'll find him. He'll be okay. It's Christian.
該直升機系空中客車直升機公司 H130
The helicopter was an airbus helicopter h-130...
有我們可以幫到的地方嗎
Ls there anything we can do?
儘管克裡斯汀-格雷才27歲
And Christian grey, although only 27 years old,
但他有豐富的飛行經驗
had extensive flying experience.
好吧 再見
All right, bye.
格雷是西雅圖 最年輕的億萬富翁
One of Seattle's youngest billionaires,
他是格雷股份有限公司的總裁
grey's the charismatic head of grey enterprises holdings,
這是跨國大企業
a multinational conglomerate...
天啊 有誰能讓他們閉嘴嗎?
Jesus! Will someone shut them up?
別 就讓它們開著吧
No, please. Leave it on.
何塞 麻煩你 聲音小點
Just turn it down please, Jose.
謝謝
Thank you.
你在發抖 我給你那件毛衣好嗎?
You're shivering. I'll get you a sweater, okay?
安娜 來 喝點茶
Ana. Tea.
他會沒事的
He's gonna be fine.
他必須沒事
He has to be okay.
我們還沒有在一起多久
We haven't had any time.
我們需要更多的時間在一起
We need to have more time.
你會有大把時間的
You're going to have plenty of time.
你能出現在克裡斯汀的生活裡和我們一起
We're so glad that you're here with us
我們都很感激
and in Christian's life.
你讓他的生活變得如此不同
You've made such a difference to him.
你出現之前他總是拒人以千里之外
He never let anyone get close until you came along.
格蕾絲 他很仰慕你的
Grace, he adores you.
我知道
I know,
孩子長大了  就會離開父母 沒關係
but children grow apart from their parents, and that's fine,
只要他們快樂就好
as long as they're happy.
他和你在一起就很快樂
And he is happy with you.
這就是我一直想要的
And that's all i ever wanted.
音量大點
Turn it up.
目前發現克裡斯汀-格雷 和他的同事羅斯-貝利
Newsreader". Christian grey and his colleague ros Bailey have been found safe and well
身體並無大礙  此刻 他們也在回西雅圖 的飛機上
and are, at this moment, on their way back to Seattle.
你們都在這裡幹什麼
What the hell are you all doing here?
克裡斯汀 哦 天啊
Christian? Oh, my god!
克裡斯汀  你怎麼到這兒來的
Christian! How did you get here?
以後慢慢說 米亞
Later, Mia.
天啊 發生了什麼 你為什麼不給我打電話?
What happened? Oh, my god! Why didn't you call?
我發生了意外 手機丟了
I had an accident. I lost my phone.
我知道  所有新聞都在播
We know. It's been all over the news.
我和羅斯都沒事
I'm fine. Ros is fine.
爸爸 他在這 他剛進來的
Dad, he's here. He just walked in.
你看起來糟透了 但毫髮未損
I'm okay. He looks like shit, but he's in one piece.
他看起來 才不糟 嘿
- No, he doesn't. - Yeah, he does.
夥計們 別緊張 我沒事
Guys, relax. I'm fine.
過來 你這傢伙
Come here, man.
我的找我女朋友打聲招呼 好
Need to say hi to my girl. Okay.
行了 媽媽
Come on, mom.
我需要來一杯 我也是
- I need a drink. - Me, too.
想我了嗎?
Miss me?
哦 我的天
Oh, my god.
我以為  沒事的 安娜
I thought... Hey, hey, Ana...
沒事 安娜 我在這呢
It's all right. Ana, I'm here.
我太害怕了 太害怕了
I was so scared. I was so scared.
我以為我永遠見不到你了
I thought i lost you forever.
不可能的
Not a chance.
我在這兒
I'm here.
就在那時我所有的儀器亮了起來。
That's when all my instruments lit up.
機尾著火 兩個引擎失去動力  兩個？
- Had a fire in the tail, lost both engines. - Both of them?
是啊  謝謝。
Yeah. Thank you.
我試圖找到一個安全的地方，但周圍都是樹木。
I tried to find somewhere safe to land, but it was all trees.
我們撞到樹  幸運的是我們爬出來了
We hit them pretty hard, but luckily we were both able to crawl out of there.
謝天
Thank goodness.
謝地
Thank god.
對不起，夥計們，我得離開了。
Sorry, guys, but i gotta take off.
好吧
Okay.
何塞，很高興來到這裡
Jose, thanks for being here. Means the world to Ana.
當然。 嘿...
Of course. Hey...
歡迎回家 克裡斯汀-格雷先生
Welcome home, Mr. grey. Christian, please.
嗯，太晚了，我們應該休息了
Well, it's late, and these two should get some rest.
格雷絲 是嗎?  是的
Grace, shall we? Yes.
我想我們也要回家了，兄弟
Yeah, I think we're gonna head home too, bro.
Cool.
我來送送你們
We'll walk you guys.
雖然有點討厭這樣說 好在你男朋友沒事
Kinda hate to say this, but your guy's all right.
我很高興他沒事  我希望你也開心
I'm glad he's okay, and I'm glad you're happy.
謝謝 明天我們會看到你在聚會嗎?
Thank you. Will we be seeing you tomorrow at his party?
推不掉的
Don't push it.
過來
Come here.
我沒事
Careful.
我知道
I know.
媽媽 好了
Mom. Okay.
安娜 那我們明天見
We'll see you tomorrow, Ana.
安娜 晚安
Anastasiai good night.
都過了12點了
It's after midnight.
我一點都不疲憊
I'm not tired.
不是
No.
我是說你生日到了
It's your birthday.
對
Yeah.
生日快樂
Happy birthday.
謝謝
Thank you.
我給你的禮物還留著嗎?
Do you still have that gift I gave you?
是的
Yes.
你知道我不需要什麼禮物
You know you didn't have to.
我想要的只有你
All I want is you.
打開它吧
Just open it.
好
Okay.
鑰匙鏈
Keychain.
翻過來看
Turn it over.
是我想的那個 我願意 嗎
Does this mean yes, yes?
是的
Yes.
是的  沒錯 我願意
Yes, yes, yes.
等等
Wait!
所以答案一直都在我口袋裡揣著
So this whole time I had the answer in my pocket?
安娜斯塔西婭-斯蒂爾
Anastasia Steele...
我可那你怎麼辦才好
What am I gonna do with you?
帶我去紅房子
Take me to the red room.
帶我去
Take me...
帶我去紅房子
Take me to the red room.
你確定？ 是的
Are you sure? Yes.
是的
Yes.
我愛你。
I love you.
嗯，我愛你
Well, I love you.
Hello? Mom? Hi.
安娜，甜心 你去哪兒了？
Ana, sweetheart. Where have you been?
我知道。 我一直在...對不起 工作一直都是這麼瘋狂
I know. I've been... I'm sorry. Work has been so crazy.
我希望你不會因此過度勞累
I hope they're not overworking you?
不，不。 它實際上是...真的很好
No, no. It's actually... It's going really well.
嗯，但是我打電話是因為我，我想和你談談克裡斯汀
Um, but I was calling because I, um... i wanted to talk to you about Christian.
克裡斯汀 你聽說過他嗎？
Christian? You've heard from him?
是的,我們又在一起
Yeah. We got back together.
親愛的，太棒了！ 這次一定會持續下去
Honey, that's wonderful! This time it's going to last. I know it is.
我希望你是對的，因為...
I hope you're right, because, um...
他要我嫁給他，我同意了
He asked me to marry him, and I said yes.
媽媽?
Mom?
你不是...不，不，我沒有懷孕。
You're not... No, no, I'm not pregnant.
Um...
我知道我們沒有在一起很久，
I know that we haven't been together very long,
但我非常愛他。
but I love him so much.
他是一個。
He's the one.
哦，親愛的！ 我為你很高興！
Oh, sweetheart! I'm so happy for you!
你確定？ 當然。
You are? Of course.
你一直都知道自己的想法。
You've always known your own mind.
如果那個人是你生命的愛，你用雙手抓住他
If that man is the love of your life, you grab him with both hands.
謝謝，媽媽。
Thanks, mama.
你打電話給格雷 嗯,不,還沒有。
Have you called ray? Um, no, not yet.
克裡斯汀 他還有他的事情
Um... Christian did, though. He asked for his permission.
他向你求婚了? 這樣太可愛了
He asked for your hand? That's so chivalrous.
嘿
Hey.
嗨
香檳 格雷先生?
Champagne, Mr. grey?
謝謝 格雷琴
Thanks, Gretchen.
我能說聲祝你生日快樂嗎
And can I just say, happy birthday?
當然 謝謝
Sure. Thank you.
克裡斯汀  媽媽
Christian. Mom.
生日快樂 謝謝
Happy birthday. Thank you.
安娜 嗨
And Ana. Hi.
很高興再見到你
It's so good to see you again.
你昨晚見過我們
You saw us last night.
似的
Yes.
正因如此
And because of that
我再也不覺得什麼事是 理所當然
I am never taking anything for granted. Ever again.
嘿
Hey!
我聽說墜機事件了 你還好吧
I heard about the crash. Are you okay?
我沒事 艾琳娜 謝謝關心
I'm fine, Elena. Thank you.
哦
Oh!
安娜 我給你介紹我的好朋友  艾琳娜-林肯
Ana, let me introduce to you, my good friend, Elena Lincoln.
我們在化妝舞會上見過了
We met at the masquerade.
對 很高興再見到你
Yes. Nice to see you again.
抱歉
Excuse us.
當然
Surely.
她 太棒了
She's fantastic.
女士們 先生們 米亞
Ladies, gentlemen. Mia.
感謝今晚各位的出席
I wanna thank you all for coming here this evening.
我原以為是一場小型家庭聚會
I was expecting a small family gathering.
多謝米亞
Thanks, Mia.
但你們能來我非常高興
But I'm happy that you're all here
因為我要宣佈一件事
because I have an announcement to make.
正如你們所知我昨天和羅斯死裡逃生
As most of you know, yesterday ros and I had a narrow escape.
正是那些事敲醒了我 我知道
And something like that reminds us of what really matters
什麼才是重要的 遺跡把握每一天是多麼可貴
and how important it is to seize the day.
我們應該珍惜我們關心的人，關心我們的人。
We should Cherish the people we care about and who care about us.
媽媽，爸爸，我知道我並不是一個完美的兒子。
Mom, dad, I know I haven't always been the perfect son.
但是，我一切都歸功於你們，所以謝謝你。
But I owe everything to you both, so thank you.
所以我想公佈一些事情
But that's not the announcement.
安娜 請過來一下
Ana, come up here a second, please.
前端時間 我極其榮幸的 遇到了這個年輕貌美的女人
So, a while ago, I was lucky enough to meet this amazing young woman,
安娜斯塔西婭-斯蒂爾
Anastasia Steele.
很快我就意思到
And very quickly, l reahzed that she was the one
她是我想共度一生的伴侶
I wanted to share my life with.
所以我想她求婚了 她答應了
So I asked her to marry me, and she said yes.
哦 這太
Oh! That is so...
安娜  我太激動了
Lam thrilled, Ana.
歡迎成為我們家庭的一員 謝謝
Welcome to the family. Anastasiai thank you.
如果我在哭的的話就要脫水了
If I cry any more, I'm just going to dehydrate.
哦 別這哭了
Oh, my god! Don't do that.
恭喜
Congratulations.
別哭了 媽媽
Stop crying, mom.
止不住 我太愛你了
Can't help it. I love you so much.
我也愛你
I love you.
哥 真有你的
Hi! Well done, big brother!
戒指 給我看看戒指
Ring! Show me the ring.
我們打算一起去選
Oh, we're gonna choose it together.
竟然沒有鑽石 克裡斯汀-格雷
No rock. Christian grey.
天啊 我要有個嫂子了
Oh, my god! I have a sister!
我才離開幾周時間 事情就這樣了
I leave you alone for a couple weeks, and this is what happens?
我知道 抱歉沒有告訴你
I know! I'm sorry i didn't tell you.
哦 得了 抱一個
Oh, please. Come here.
On!
傍上西雅圖鑽石王老五感覺怎麼樣
So, how does it feel to bag Seattle's most eligible bachelor?
有點不安 但
It's a little scary, but...
他絕對非你莫屬
Well, if anyone can make it work, it's you.
嘿 嫂子
Hey, sis-in-law!
恭喜 克裡斯汀 真是個有福氣的傢伙
Congratulations. Christian's a very lucky guy.
然而你是個不折不扣的瘋子
You, however, are certifiably insane.
抱歉打斷你們
I'm sorry to interrupt.
米亞想要你嘗嘗 讓人欲罷不能的雞尾酒
Mia wants to taste one of your killer cocktails.
嗯 好的 馬上來
Oh, well, coming right up.
看來我們的談話讓你受益匪淺
I see you heeded our little talk.
你憑什麼覺得我會聽你的
What makes you think i would ever listen to you?
你根本不在乎克裡斯汀
You don't care about Christian.
他會明白的
He'll see that.
我保證會讓他明白的
I'll make sure of it.
他會看穿你的詭計
He'll see right through you.
艾琳娜 你玩完了
It's over for you, Elena.
你只是垂涎他財產的小角色
You're just a mousy little thing after his money.
他根本沒法駕馭婚姻
He's not capable of marriage.
謝謝你 克裡斯汀
Thank you, Christian.
艾琳娜 你為什麼在這裡
Why are you even here, Elena?
她不適合你
She's not right for you.
你不明白什麼才適合我
You don't know what's right for me.
艾琳娜 你教會我床笫之事
You taught me how to fuck, Elena.
而安娜教會了我如何去愛
Ana taught me how to love.
她只是你的一個備胎
She's just the next one in line.
從我家滾出去
Get out of my house.
別碰我的孩子 從我家滾出去
Leave my children alone, and get the hell out of my house.
安娜 親愛的
Ana, darling...
麻煩讓我們單獨談談 好嗎?
Would you give us a moment alone, please?
抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
你媽媽還好嗎?
Ls your mom okay?
簡直怒髮衝冠
Furious. Hmm.
艾琳娜走啦
Elena's gone.
是結束了那種走了嗎
Like, gone, gone?
不管生意上
I'm done.
還是生活上 都結束了
The business. Everything.
我明天會召集員工落實細節
I'll have my people sort out the details tomorrow.
我知道她對你很重要
I know she was important to you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你真的覺得抱歉嗎?
Are you?
不是 這就對了
No. No.
你手裡拿的是什麼
What's that you got there?
跟我來 我給你看樣東西
Come with me. There's something I need to show you.
上次我們下來的時候我還被你扛在肩膀上
Last time we came down here, i was over your shoulder.
是的
Oh, yeah.
你先走
After you.
哦我的天
Oh, my god!
你喜歡的愛心和花束
You wanted hearts and flowers.
哦 我的天
Oh, my god!
沒事
It's okay.
克裡斯汀
Christian...
這太讓人震驚了
This is amazing.
嫁給我
Be mine.
與我共度餘生
Share my life with me.
我願意
Yes.
嫁給我
Marry me.
我會嫁給你
I'll marry you.
給我你的手
Give me your hand.
這也是你安排的?
Did you do that?
太棒了 快看
Great, isn't it? That's so pretty.
Oh!
我莊嚴地發誓
I solemnly vow
忠實地愛你
to love you faithfully
保證你的安全，一直過下去
and to keep you safe for as long as we both shall live.